and the best they are increasing [Music]
以及他们正在增加的最好的东西[音乐]
renee zellweger [Applause]
蕾妮·齐薇格[鼓掌]
[Music]
[音乐]
[Music] [Applause]
[音乐] [掌声]
[Music] ever used the term a few so at this very
[音乐]曾经在这个词上使用过一些
heavy [Laughter]
重[笑声]
thank you to bridge god give him a kiss so that online social scarlet jazzy
谢谢你桥接上帝给他一个吻，让网络上的猩红色爵士乐
but another to manage kids night Feb 16 superstar
但是另一位来管理孩子们的夜晚2月16日是超级巨星
our dad who got in trouble to splash this set on her voice new
我们的父亲遇到麻烦，将这套装置泼在她的新声音上
elevage thingy push and unlike you and height mario and hamster grateful for a
高高的东西推，与您不同，身高的马里奥和仓鼠感激不尽
collaboration and key for french thank you and this in the park and we
合作和法国人的钥匙谢谢你，这在公园里，我们
sending it to the orchestra coloring the weather girls is one
发送给乐团给天气女孩上色是一个
some there are only in the audience the therapy and braille it is so loud
有些听众中只有疗法和盲文，声音很大
race and water and your treasure memories a timeshare with
种族与水和您的宝藏与之分时共处
citycard ghent in the box the account and go on like 'to knit to in a fir
帐户中的citycard ghent帐户，然后继续进行下去，例如“编织成杉树”
so asselt enqueue my team we come here thank you and me
如此让我们的团队入队，我们来这里谢谢你和我
protest in crime david livingstone and more sales thank you for your peace
抗议犯罪大卫·利文斯通和更多销售感谢您的安宁
fresh fresh watch experience thank you for your time and for you m
新鲜的新鲜手表体验，谢谢您的时间，也感谢您。
ethan baxter dawes giffords jeremy for your magic make a
ethan baxter dawes giffords jeremy为您的魔术做出了
she rather dead unbelievable cross teams and her frank lammers becoming mine
她宁愿死掉令人难以置信的交叉团队，也没有坦率的lammers成为我的
computer but then cree chip firmer
电脑，但随后CREE芯片变硬
i don't give one and paul chandler am luke challenger and judy dicky
我不给任何人，保罗·钱德勒是卢克·挑战者和朱迪·迪基
no milk and to hear and dress first point in your pc moment and free one
没有牛奶，可以听到并穿上电脑时的第一点，并有空
and then all mackerel I put you third in that this to the base in the
然后我把所有鲭鱼放到第三位，
city ​​where you enter there financially air your final days there film recently
您进入那里的城市最近播放电影的最后几天
the batala scepter made in this town where you can sunbathe the futures
在这个小镇上制造的巴塔拉权杖，您可以在这里晒日光浴
3-leaf clover celebrator and family share this experience and
三叶草三叶草的庆祝者和家人分享了这一经验，
saving with you is the man my life scrapers
和你一起拯救是我生命中的刮胡刀
fear and then silent series of mist garment london town which i have always feel so
恐惧，然后是我一直感觉如此的伦敦服装小镇的无声系列
much suppose your work is so before you think there
假设您的工作是如此，然后再考虑
someone like me
跟我一样的人